<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shoko</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/</link><description>Recent content on Shoko</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://docs.shokoanime.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/index.json</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/index.json</guid><description/></item><item><title>Configure Shokofin</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokofin/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokofin/configuration/</guid><description>The Configuration page is still a WIP. In the meantime until it goes live then I will suggest asking in our discord server if you need help configuring the plugin.</description></item><item><title>First Run Setup</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/setup/</guid><description>Initializing Server After you&amp;rsquo;ve installed Shoko Server, run it so it can initialize which should only take a couple of seconds. As Shoko Server uses a Web UI, nothing will initially open so you&amp;rsquo;ll need to click on the Shoko Server icon in your tray and click Web UI to open the browser based UI. You can also access the Web UI by typing in http://localhost:8111/ in your browser&amp;rsquo;s address bar.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/faq/</guid><description>Frequently Asked Questions The following are frequent questions we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled in one place to better help our users. For more in-depth information on a particular subject, we suggest checking the related page (if available in the documentation. Additional support can be found by joining our Discord server using the Support link located in the footer.</description></item><item><title>Install Shokofin</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokofin/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokofin/install/</guid><description>Requirements The plugin requires a version of Jellyfin greater or equal to 10.7.0 (&amp;gt;=10.7.0) and an unstable version of Shoko Server greater or equal to 4.1.1 (&amp;gt;=4.1.1) to be installed. It also requires that you have already set up and are using Shoko Server, and that the directories/folders you intend to use in Jellyfin are fully indexed (and optionally managed) by Shoko Server, otherwise the plugin won&amp;rsquo;t be able to funciton properly — it won&amp;rsquo;t be able to find metadata about any entries that are not indexed by Shoko Server since the metadata we want is not available.</description></item><item><title>Installing &amp; Configuring My Anime 3</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/myanime3/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/myanime3/install/</guid><description>Is Shoko Server Mandatory? My Anime 3 is not a standalone plugin and requires Shoko Server installed, configured and running in order to work properly. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t done this yet, Download Shoko Server from our main website and use the installation guides located in the menu on the left to properly install and configure Shoko Server.
My Anime 3 - Future DevelopmentMy Anime 3 is no longer in active development and has entered maintenance mode.</description></item><item><title>Installing Shoko Desktop</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/desktop/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/desktop/install/</guid><description>Windows Navigate to the Shoko Downloads page and download Shoko Desktop, unless told otherwise, we always recommend downloading the Stable version. The installer will guide you through the installation process and should only take a couple of minutes.
Linux with Wine using Bottles Install Bottles (https://usebottles.com). This may require installing Flatpak and adding the Flathub repository if you don&amp;rsquo;t have it already. Before adding a bottle, go to Bottles preferences and under the &amp;ldquo;Runners&amp;rdquo; tab, install the latest Caffe or Proton GE.</description></item><item><title>Installing Shoko Metadata</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokometadata/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokometadata/install/</guid><description>Is Shoko Server Mandatory? Shoko Metadata is not a standalone plugin and requires Shoko Server installed, configured and running in order to work properly. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t done this yet, Download Shoko Server from our main website and use the installation guides located in the menu on the left to properly install and configure Shoko Server.
Installing Shoko Metadata Shoko Metadata has to be manually installed so make sure to follow the instructions below.</description></item><item><title>Installing Shoko Server</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/install/</guid><description>Is Shoko Server Mandatory? The short answer, Yes.
Shoko Server is where all the magic happens. It acts as a central database for every program and plugin under the Shoko suite allowing you to access, maintain and watch your anime collection. This also means that Shoko Server must be running to use any other program or plugin that connect to it. Outside of file importing, Shoko Server is no more resource intensive than other programs you probably have running in the background, so you don&amp;rsquo;t need to worry about Shoko Server eating up resources.</description></item><item><title>My Anime 3 Changelog</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/myanime3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/myanime3/</guid><description>The Shoko Server Changelog is automatically outputted. To update it, please edit the server.json file in data/changelog.</description></item><item><title>My Anime 3 Overview</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/myanime3/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/myanime3/overview/</guid><description>Accessing My Anime 3 Like with any MediaPortal plugin, you can access My Anime 3 from the plugins list on your menu.
Once its loaded, the filter list will appear offering a variety of default filters as well as any user added ones. If you want to create new filters or edit existing ones, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to use Shoko Desktop. Select a filter that&amp;rsquo;s populated, depending on the amount of entries in that filter it might take a few seconds to load.</description></item><item><title>Search Shoko</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/search/</guid><description>Input Search Criteria Below The embedded Google Search below will allow you to search through the Shoko website and Shoko Docs.</description></item><item><title>Setting Up Shoko Metadata</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokometadata/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/shokometadata/setup/</guid><description>Creating A Shoko Library With Shoko Server running, open Plex and either select Movies or TV Shows. Note if you did not do the edit mentioned on the Shoko Metadata Install page to combine the libraries, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to repeat these steps for the other library.
When asked to select the Media Folder, browse to your anime collection. Even though Shoko will be providing the metadata, Plex still needs to know where the physical files are located.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Metadata</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/shokometadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/shokometadata/</guid><description>The Shoko Server Changelog is automatically outputted. To update it, please edit the server.json file in data/changelog.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server Changelog</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/desktop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/desktop/</guid><description>The Shoko Server Changelog is automatically outputted. To update it, please edit the server.json file in data/changelog.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server Changelog</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/server/</guid><description>The Shoko Server Changelog is automatically outputted. To update it, please edit the server.json file in data/changelog.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server Web UI</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/webui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/webui/</guid><description>The Shoko Server Changelog is automatically outputted. To update it, please edit the server.json file in data/changelog.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Website Translation</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/translate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/translate/</guid><description>Lets Translate! First off, we want to say thank you for taking the time to translate the Shoko Website! Our goal is to reach as many users as possible and by translating the website, you&amp;rsquo;re helping us make that happen.
We&amp;rsquo;ve made this quick guide to hopefully make the process easier, please let us know if there are any issues or if you have any ideas on improving it.
Code EditsWhile we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to make it as easy as possible, there are a few code edits that need to be made.</description></item><item><title>Shokofin</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/shokofin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/changelog/shokofin/</guid><description>The Shoko Server Changelog is automatically outputted. To update it, please edit the server.json file in data/changelog.</description></item></channel></rss>