<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Servers on Shoko Docs</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/</link><description>Recent content in Servers on Shoko Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoko Server - Configure Settings</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/config/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/config/</guid><description>What Are Actions? By default, all tasks related to maintaining and updating your collection are done automatically. By default, every task runs on a timer, these timers determine how often certain data sets are updated which in most cases, works just fine. However, for various reasons you may need to run one of these tasks manually which is made possible by using an Action. Most actions are comprised of multiple related tasks with the action name relating to the task or tasks it performs.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server - Linux Setup</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/install_linux/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/install_linux/</guid><description>Is Shoko Server Mandatory? The short answer is Yes.
Shoko Server is the back-end of the entire Shoko suite, which means every single program and plugin provided uses it for accessing and maintaining your anime collection. This makes Shoko Server mandatory and also means Shoko Server must be running to use any of the programs or plugins that connect to it. With the exception of file importing, Shoko Server is no more resource intensive than other programs you probably have running in the background so you don&amp;rsquo;t need to worry about Shoko Server eating up resources.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server - Web UI</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/webui/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/webui/</guid><description>Disclaimer Please note, we&amp;rsquo;re currently working on a rewrite of Shoko Docs and such the information below is outdated. However it should get you headed in the right direction, join our Discord server if you need additional help. Accessing The Web UI Depending on the OS you&amp;rsquo;re using, accessing the Web UI can be done using one of the following methods.
Please note, the examples provided are based on the default settings.</description></item><item><title>Shoko Server - Windows Setup</title><link>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/install_windows/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.shokoanime.com/server/install_windows/</guid><description>Is Shoko Server Mandatory? The short answer is Yes.
Shoko Server is the back-end of the entire Shoko suite, which means every single program and plugin provided uses it for accessing and maintaining your anime collection. This makes Shoko Server mandatory and also means Shoko Server must be running to use any of the programs or plugins that connect to it. With the exception of file importing, Shoko Server is no more resource intensive than other programs you probably have running in the background so you don&amp;rsquo;t need to worry about Shoko Server eating up resources.</description></item></channel></rss>